This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now this is exciting!
Can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Separated from the rest of his crew, Luffy has finally arrived at Marineford
to rescue his brother Ace.
Aided by new friends and old enemies alike,
Luffy battles against the Navy as he pushes towards the scaffold.
Thanks to a final charge from Whitebeard's associates and a bridge built by Inazuma,
success is within Luffy's grasp at long last.
Finally, I'm here!
I told you I'd do it!
Luffy?
You really are crazy.
Fire!
Blow them to bits before they hit the ground!
What is that?
It looks like a tunnel of flames!
Ever since you were little, you've never listened to a word I said.
Have you?
Then you run off and do something crazy!
Like old times, huh Luffy?
Let's go!
Ace Rescue, Whitebeard's final order!
That's Fire Fist Ace!
Ace Free!
Yee-haw!
You did a straw hat!
Yeah!
Ha ha!
You can suck it, Navy!
He hasn't slowed down once after all he's been through!
You can't stop this guy!
Your papa would be so proud!
I knew you could do it.
But this is only the beginning of your long, happy ending.
With me at your side, of course.
Because as soon as you escape this wretched battlefield,
we'll be married!
See that?
He really did it!
That crazy little bastard saved Ace!
Of course he did.
After all, he's Luffy.
Keep your cool!
This isn't over yet!
Open fire as soon as they land!
Sir!
Let's split up for now!
Don't let your guard down yet!
Okay!
Wait, no!
Flame Commandment!
Fire pillar!
Whoa!
They're strong! Be careful, men!
Can you still fight, Luffy?
Of course I can!
Luffy! Ace!
Remember, Ace is a Logia Titan, so he's gonna be really tough to hit.
Never thought I'd need my little brother to save me.
Guess I'll swallow my pride this time.
I owe you one, Luffy.
Thanks, but I sure couldn't have done it if Whitebeard hadn't shown up.
You think we'll let you get away?
Consider this your execution ground, pirates!
Now charge!
I'll cut him to pieces!
That's my little brother you're trying to murder.
I'll have to ask you to stop!
Fire Fist!
No!
Now!
Second gear!
Save!
Hm?
Come come!
Boom!
Daddy!
Fire gun!
You're dead!
This is fun and all, but the sooner we leave this delta,
the better, right?
They're a fine team, I dare say.
We're pulling out! Clear a path!
We can't let them get away!
Firefly!
Fiery dog!
This isn't over yet! Execute them both!
Now go, go!
Go!
Get ready!
What?
I gotta commit, you've gotten pretty tough, Luffy.
I've got to admit, you've gotten pretty tough, Luffy.
One of these days, I'll be stronger than you.
All right, then I'll handle things in the meantime.
One of these days. Sorry, kid.
You're not gonna survive to see tomorrow, I'm afraid.
Go finish him off, Admiral.
What a pain.
All right, ice block.
Stand back, Luffy.
And now, Pheasant Beak! Flame Mirror!
And now, Pheasant Beak!
Ah!
He vaporized Aokiji's ice.
Damn, I didn't know you could do that.
Well, I can't blame Ace for showing off a bit.
It's been a long time coming.
Whoa.
A pair of brothers?
That's so cool.
Now's not the time to be impressed.
Unless you're impressed with me, that is.
In other words, fix that transponder snail so I can show off again.
Right, of course, Captain.
Go ahead, Straw Hat.
Enjoy your time in the limelight,
because everything's about to come crashing down.
And the biggest crash is going to be Whitebeard
after I take his head in all this chaos.
He's got to be on his last leg anyway.
I'll be one of the four emperors in no time.
Wow.
No matter how dicey the situation gets,
Captain Buggy always greets it with a smile.
Yeah!
Mr. Two, I hope I could honor your memory in my own humble way.
Anywho, that's enough heroism for a lifetime.
I'm leaving.
Which platoon is this traitor from?
Go!
Hold on!
He's a prisoner impersonating a guard!
No!
I was too slow!
You're all right, sir?
This is the worst blunder of my life.
We have to rectify this.
Just let him go.
It makes things more interesting, I say.
Cut the crap.
Those guys went toe-to-toe with an admiral.
What the hell are we supposed to do?
Pull yourselves together.
Admiral Sakazuki!
They won't make it out of here alive.
Don't you worry.
Don't give up, men!
We've got this!
Great!
What the hell is it now?
The enemy ship is coming through!
Uh, on land somehow!
Don't get close!
It's running on the ground with its paddles!
Wait!
Who's on board?
I can't see!
It's Squarn!
And it looks like he's got his crew with him, too!
Make a break for it, Pops!
We'll guard you!
We'll show those bastards the pride of the Spider World Pirates!
God damn it!
What are you thinking?
Don't be an idiot, squad!
You'll die!
Yeah!
You got a death wish or something?
Yes.
Of course.
After what I did to Pops, this is the least I can do.
I can't hope to atone for my crime, but if I don't die fighting here, I know I'll never
rest in peace.
I'm sorry for bringing you with me.
This should be my fight.
What?
Are you kidding me?
We wanted to follow you.
Yeah, you're our captain.
To the bitter end.
If we all die here, then that's our choice.
Let's not get sentimental here.
Lead the charge, captain!
Thank you.
Everyone else grab Ace!
And make a run for it!
St. Helmer's Fire!
Squad?
Those fools.
Squad...
No.
You think anyone's gonna be happy with a plan like this?
Hey!
Hurry up and get these cuffs off of me!
You ready?
We'll fight to the last man!
Yeah!
All right, charge!
Four pops!
What the hell?
Did we run into something?
Huh?
What the...?
But why, pops?
He stopped him with one hand!
I thought he was supposed to be dying!
you believe you've done me a favor you poor selfish child don't you know how cruel it is to force a
father to bury his own sons and show some humility you think i'm on my last legs because of one measly
poke it was settled long before i came here everyone has to grow old and die someday
our business is done pull out now and i'll stay here to make sure i don't lose any more of my
boys to these bastards you're staying what do you mean
listen up whitebeard pirates and listen well
these are my final orders as your captain so you better follow them you're kidding right
that's the last thing we want to hear we're going back together yeah we can't go on without you we
didn't save ace to let our captain die crossfire let's go even family must part ways now and then
you must survive return to the new world continue your legacy without me
no you can't die we can find another way
make no mistake i'm a relic of a bygone era
long have i sailed but no ship can carry me into the new age
now go and forge your own path
there's no way we can leave you here look i know how you feel but it's an order
hulk i know what are you
don't look back boys
a new age is coming
you
Thank you.
Everything started on those warm waters.
Oh man, what a hole!
Hey, you don't even care about treasure, you weirdo.
Come check it out. There's plenty to go around, buddy.
Forget it. He's always like this.
Huh? What does that mean?
We wouldn't even have these treasures without him.
Whatever. It's nothing to complain about.
If he doesn't care, then neither should we.
But it's weird. Pirates live for the booty.
Why else would you be in the game?
Well, what are you looking for, then?
Hey, you listening, Newgate?
It's been a long journey, but a good one.
Let's finally put an end to this.
You Navy bastards!
The Whitebeard Pirates reluctantly follow the captain's final order to retreat.
However, Aka-Inu refuses to let his enemies escape and provokes Ace by insulting his adoptive father.
Ace fights to defend the honor of his crew, but risks losing his life in the process.
On the next, One Piece, the power that can burn even fire, Aka-Inu's ruthless pursuit, I'm gonna be king of the pirates!